<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<selectionList id="b91294ca-5f2a-43ac-bcba-7d331fdf4bc1">
  <descriptionCdata><![CDATA[b91294ca-5f2a-43ac-bcba-7d331fdf4bc1.description=<pre>\nWindows PowerShell execution policies let you determine the conditions under which Windows PowerShell loads configuration files and runs scripts. You can set an execution policy for the local computer, for the current user, or for a particular session. You can also use a Group Policy setting to set execution policy for computers and users.\n\nThe Windows PowerShell execution policies are as follows\:\n\n1. "Restricted" is the default policy.\n\t- Default execution policy.\n\t- Permits individual commands, but will not run scripts. \n\t- Prevents running of all script files, including formatting and configuration files (.ps1xml), module script files (.psm1), and Windows PowerShell profiles (.ps1).  \n    \n2. "AllSigned"\n\t- Scripts can run.\n\t- Requires that all scripts and configuration files be signed by a trusted publisher, including scripts that you write on the local computer.\n\t- Prompts you before running scripts from publishers that you have not yet classified as trusted or untrusted.\n\t- Risks running unsigned scripts from sources other than the Internet and signed, but malicious, scripts.\n      \n3. "RemoteSigned"\n\t- Scripts can run.\n\t- Requires a digital signature from a trusted publisher on scripts and configuration files that are downloaded from the Internet (including e-mail and instant messaging programs).\n\t- Does not require digital signatures on scripts that you have run and that you have written on the local computer (not downloaded from the Internet).\n\t- Risks running signed, but malicious, scripts.\n\n4. "Unrestricted"\n\t- Unsigned scripts can run. (This risks running malicious scripts.)\n\t- Warns the user before running srcipts and configuration files that are downloaded from the Internet.  \n\n5. "Bypass"\n\t- Nothing is blocked and there are no warnings or prompts.\n\t- This execution policy is designed for configurations in which a Windows PowerShell script is built in to a a larger application or for configurations in which Windows PowerShell is the foundation for a program that has its own security model.\n\n6. "Undefined"\n\t- There is no execution policy set in the current scope.\n\t- If the execution policy in all scopes is Undefined, the effective execution policy is Restricted, which is the default execution policy.\n\nNote\: On systems that do not distinguish Universal Naming Convention (UNC) paths from Internet paths, scripts that are identified by a UNC path might not be permitted to run with the RemoteSigned execution policy. \n</pre>
]]></descriptionCdata>
  <annotation>b91294ca-5f2a-43ac-bcba-7d331fdf4bc1.description</annotation>
  <name>Windows PowerShell Execution Policy</name>
  <storage>
    <string>Restricted</string>
    <string>AllSigned</string>
    <string>RemoteSigned</string>
    <string>Unrestricted</string>
    <string>Bypass</string>
    <string>Undefined</string>
  </storage>
</selectionList>